Guide to the Arleen Schloss Papers MSS.437
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII. Audiovisual Recordings, 1950-2007; 16 VHS; 16 Hi8; 15 MiniDV; 9 U-matic; 4 audiocassette; 1 DAT; 1 16mm_film_reels
  Series VII. Audiovisual Recordings contains recordings that could not be arranged into series based on their labels alone.
  Series VII. Audiovisual Recordings is arranged chronologically. Undated materials are arranged alphabetically following the chronological listing.
  - Mac B/U micronet, 1950 (Box 84, Dat 437_0792)
  - Story, Image ET Technique, 1964
    - Video (Box 144, Vhs 437_2143)
    - Video (Box 106, Minidv 437_2300)
  - Audio A-2, 1974-1984 (Box 86, Audiocassette 437_0874)
  - Instant Burn Water #6, June 16, 1982 (Box 141, U-matic 437_1903)
  - Gospel -- D.C., Reel II, September, 1983 (Box 134, U-matic 437_1825)
  - MM 84, 1984 (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0142)
  - #1A, May 13-26, 1988 (Box 103, Hi8 437_2209)
  - Trees, scientists, June 13-16, 1988 (Box 103, Hi8 437_2210)
  - 50th, tape 2, twisted tape, 1991 (Box 89, Hi8 437_1246)
  - "Machida Machizura" -- Bifukudan Doterai Yakura, circa 1991 (Box 68, Audiocassette 437_0134)
  - Dr. John Wheeler, May - June, 1993
    - Video, May 25, 1993 (Box 101, Hi8 437_2068)
    - Video, May 25, 1993 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2314)
    - Video, May - June, 1993 (Box 137, Vhs 437_1777)
    - Dr. John Wheeler and Peter test, undated (Box 106, Minidv 437_2296)
  - Temple Emmanuel, March 21, 1994 (Box 100, Hi8 437_2040)
  - #1 Stuff at Buntetor, January, 1994 (Box 136, Vhs 437_1758)
  - DD, 1996 (Box 90, Hi8 437_1258)
  - Dalia recovery yoga, hotel, July - August, 2000 (Box 106, Minidv 437_2325)
  - Material DVD, 2004 (Box 96, Minidv 437_1524)
  - Willoughby Sharp, October 12, 2007 (Box 107, Minidv 437_2392)
  - #1 Dog's Life, undated (Box 91, Hi8 437_1281)
  - #5 HG, Ron Reissman, undated (Box 137, Vhs 437_1810)
  - #14 September 14/15, undated (Box 98, Hi8 437_1997)
  - A I V ? !, undated (Box 103, Hi8 437_2189)
  - Agrippa, undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1770)
  - Ali Hilites - Signs #12, undated (Box 134, U-matic 437_1820)
  - "Agents of Paradise", undated (Box 106, Minidv 437_2317)
  - Arleen after W, undated (Box 89, Minidv 437_2409)
  - Arleen Schloss, undated (Box 140, Vhs 437_1868)
  - Arleen Schloss, undated (Box 137, Vhs 437_1799)
  - Arleen Schloss, undated (Box 137, Vhs 437_1803)
  - Arleen Schloss, undated (Box 99, Hi8 437_2025)
  - Arleen Schloss, undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1739)
  - Chi Kung, undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1741)
  - Copy, undated (Box 91, Hi8 437_1293)
  - Copy, undated (Box 90, Hi8 437_1275)
  - "Devil Wears Prada", undated (Box 144, Vhs 437_2155)
  - Dia, undated (Box 135, Vhs 437_1733)
  - Digital sound I, undated (Box 89, Hi8 437_1247)
  - Dr. Dalia Zwick assisting Arleen Schloss, undated (Box 143, Vhs 437_1925)
  - Dhalia Zwick Dub, undated (Box 107, Minidv 437_2383)
  - Golem -- images, master edit, copy, undated (Box 99, Hi8 437_2029)
  - Guided yoga, guided body scan, undated (Box 67, Audiocassette 437_2415)
  - "How to Draw a Bunny", undated
    - Part one (Box 96, Minidv 437_1525)
    - Part two (Box 106, Minidv 437_2335)
  - Janice Krasnow -- "How to Get Along with Other People", undated (Box 100, Hi8 437_2037)
  - Nik #3, July 28, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1528)
  - Opening 2, Friday, undated (Box 125, U-matic 437_1229)
  - PCM #2 III, IV, V, undated (Box 90, Hi8 437_1263)
  - Reci, undated (Box 85, Minidv 437_2277)
  - Steve's camera, undated (Box 96, Minidv 437_1469)
  - Susi's Riptide, undated (Box 136, Vhs 437_1764)
  - Tape 65, TC #04, undated (Box 121, U-matic 437_1226)
  - Tape 58, TC #18, undated (Box 121, U-matic 437_1227)
  - Tape 63, TC #23, undated (Box 121, U-matic 437_1228)
  - Tape 60, TC #20, undated (Box 125, U-matic 437_1231)
  - Tape 62, TC #22, undated (Box 126, U-matic 437_1240)
  - Weeds nett next, undated (Box 138, Vhs 437_1834)
  - "Ya!", undated (Box 106, Minidv 437_2334)